<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">ConstrackerOK</string>
    <string name="title_activity_language" translatable="false">LanguageActivity</string>
    <string name="please_select_your_language_ns_il_vous_pla_t_s_lectionnez_la_langue" translatable="false">Please select your language\nS\'il vous plaît, sélectionnez la langue</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">WelcomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search_conference">SearchConference</string>
    <string name="title_activity_conference_data">ConferenceData</string>
    <string name="title_activity_log_in_speaker_space">LogInSpeakerSpace</string>
    <string name="title_activity_create_account">CreateAccount</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profils_informations">ProfilsInformations</string>
    <string name="title_activity_speaker_space">SpeakerSpace</string>
    <string name="title_activity_propose_topic">ProposeTopic</string>
    <string name="search_a_conference">Search a conference</string>
    <string name="speaker_space">Speaker space</string>
    <string name="want_to_be_a_speaker">Want to be a speaker?</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="to">To:</string>
    <string name="from">From:</string>
    <string name="your_suitable_date">Your suitable date</string>
    <string name="inscription">Inscription</string>
    <string name="click_there_if_you_agree_with_our_conditions_of_use">Click there if you agree with our conditions of use</string>
    <string name="speaker_info">Speaker info</string>
    <string name="speaker">Speaker:</string>
    <string name="duration_info">Duration info</string>
    <string name="hour_info">Hour info</string>
    <string name="duration">Duration:</string>
    <string name="date_info">Date info</string>
    <string name="your_new_topic">Your new topic</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUs</string>
    <string name="about_us_longtext">Conference Tracker will save you a lot of time and manual work by automating time-consuming conference management tasks. This automation will also increase the accuracy of your data and will enhance the overall attendee experience at your conference. Since Conference Tracker is a cloud-based system, you can sign in to the system, perform tasks, and generate reports from anywhere with just a web browser. You can even view activities at the conference without having to be at the conference site! Simply log in to your Conference Tracker account. The following list highlights the main Conference Tracker functions: Attendee Registration: Create your own online attendee registration form. The system can even take credit card payments. For additional safety, the funds will be processed via your PayPal account. If you do not have a PayPal account, they are easy and free to set up. Exhibitor Registration: Create an exhibitor registration form and collect payment from exhibitors. Conference Badge Generation: Design your conference badges and print them for your attendees, exhibitors, presenters, and staff. Use special perforated badge paper, or simply use regular or card stock paper! The printing can be done on standard office printer, which saves you the cost of buying or leasing specialized equipment. Conference Check-in: Quickly check attendees to the conference. Keep track of handouts distribution like the conference bag. Get notified when a VIP or a person of special needs checks in. Attendance Tracking at Sessions and Events: Easily track attendance at your sessions by simply scanning the attendee badge at the door. Say goodbye to outdated and cumbersome barcode scanners and use off-the-shelf Apple devices instead (iPod touch, iPad, or iPhone). Record multipole in/out of the attendee per session, and let the system figure out the attendance time. View the scans LIVE as they occur. The scans are uploaded to the cloud in real-time. However, if you do not have Internet at the session, the scans will be saved to the Apple device and will be uploaded later when you get the connection. Credit Calculations: Let Conference Tracker calculate the Continuing Education Units (CEU), Continuing Medical Education (CME), Professional Development Credits, or other attendance credits each attendee earned at the conference. Communication: Easily send an email message to all your attendees, presenters, exhibitors, or staff. Or send an email message to the attendees of a certain session. Use mail merge for a more customized message. Attendance Certificate Generation: Use Conference Tracker to design your customized attendance certificates. Create the layout and text and add signatures and graphics. Conference Tracker will automatically add each attendee\'s name and attendance credits, if any. Print out the certificates or have Conference Tracker deliver them via email. Conference Analytics: Run this handy tool to know things like your most popular sessions, busiest times, and number of attendees per session. Use this for better planning for your next conference. Figure out which session to offer in the future and plan your rooms accordingly. Data Export: Easily export your attendance data to Excel or CSV to use in other applications.</string>
    <string name="about_us_long_text">Conference Tracker will save you a lot of time and manual work by automating time-consuming conference management tasks. This automation will also increase the accuracy of your data and will enhance the overall attendee experience at your conference. Since Conference Tracker is a cloud-based system, you can sign in to the system, perform tasks, and generate reports from anywhere with just a web browser. You can even view activities at the conference without having to be at the conference site! Simply log in to your Conference Tracker account. The following list highlights the main Conference Tracker functions: 1. Attendee Registration: Create your own online attendee registration form. The system can even take credit card payments. For additional safety, the funds will be processed via your PayPal account. If you do not have a PayPal account, they are easy and free to set up. 2. Exhibitor Registration: Create an exhibitor registration form and collect payment from exhibitors. 3. Conference Badge Generation: Design your conference badges and print them for your attendees, exhibitors, presenters, and staff. Use special perforated badge paper, or simply use regular or card stock paper! The printing can be done on standard office printer, which saves you the cost of buying or leasing specialized equipment. 4. Conference Check-in: Quickly check attendees to the conference. Keep track of handouts distribution like the conference bag. Get notified when a VIP or a person of special needs checks in. 5. Attendance Tracking at Sessions and Events: Easily track attendance at your sessions by simply scanning the attendee badge at the door. Say goodbye to outdated and cumbersome barcode scanners and use off-the-shelf Apple devices instead (iPod touch, iPad, or iPhone). Record multipole in/out of the attendee per session, and let the system figure out the attendance time. View the scans LIVE as they occur. The scans are uploaded to the cloud in real-time. However, if you do not have Internet at the session, the scans will be saved to the Apple device and will be uploaded later when you get the connection. 6. Credit Calculations: Let Conference Tracker calculate the Continuing Education Units (CEU), Continuing Medical Education (CME), Professional Development Credits, or other attendance credits each attendee earned at the conference. 7. Communication: Easily send an email message to all your attendees, presenters, exhibitors, or staff. Or send an email message to the attendees of a certain session. Use mail merge for a more customized message. 8. Attendance Certificate Generation: Use Conference Tracker to design your customized attendance certificates. Create the layout and text and add signatures and graphics. Conference Tracker will automatically add each attendee\'s name and attendance credits, if any. Print out the certificates or have Conference Tracker deliver them via email. 9. Conference Analytics: Run this handy tool to know things like your most popular sessions, busiest times, and number of attendees per session. Use this for better planning for your next conference. Figure out which session to offer in the future and plan your rooms accordingly. 10. Data Export: Easily export your attendance data to Excel or CSV to use in other applications.</string>
</resources>
